გიორგი მაკასარაშვილი/George Makasarashvili

City: Tbilisi

B. Date: 30-Nov-2001

E-mail: giorgimakasarashvili@gmail.com Phone number: +995 571 70 66 32

I am a student now studying at Caucasus University (3rd year), Computer Science. In terms of Web Development, I have excellent knowledge and experience in HTML, CSS(Sass/Scss), JavaScript (JQuery), Vue.js. For 6 months I have been working on real projects, some of them are already up and running. Also, I have some personal projects built using Vue.js and a little experience of Typescript, React and Angular. In terms of Backend, I know Python (Flask) and have basic knowledge of PHP. I have experience and knowledge of SQL, I can work with data in Relational Database Management System (RDBMS), create data bases and write procedures, also I have basic knowledge at C, C++, Racket, Algorithms and Data structures.

I am detail-oriented, quick learner, analytical thinker and organized with a high sense of responsibility.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer – UpWork – front end development (2021-2022)
Freelancer – Fiverr – front end development (2021-2022)
Acceleration Program – Unilab – front end development (2022-2023)

EDUCATION

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery • 2019 • W3schools.com and freecodecamp.com COMPUTER SCIENCE • 2020 - PRESENT • CAUCASUS UNIVERSITY Vue • 2022 • The Complete Guide (incl. Router & Composition API) • udemy.com Introduction to Computer Science • 2022 • CS50 • cs50.harvard.edu Python Basics for Data Science • 2023 • courses.edx.org Analyzing Data with Python • 2023 • courses.edx.org Visualizing Data with Python • 2023 • courses.edx.org

LANGUAGES

WEBSITE

Georgian: Native English: B2

gio-makasa.github.io

HARD SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Sass/Scss | Bootstrap 5 | W3.CSS | JavaScript – ES5/ES6 | Vue.JS (Vuex) | TypeScript | JQuery | AJAX | API | JSON | OOP | Git (GitFlow) | SQL (MSSQL, PostgreSQL) | Python | Figma | Microsoft office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint | Data Analysis

BASIC: PHP | React | Angular | C/C++ | Racket | Algorithms and Data structures

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership | Collaboration/Teamwork | Time Management | Problem Solving | Critical thinking | Attention to detail | Flexibility/Adaptability | Self Motivated | Accountability | Responsibility | Strong organizational skills